CONTACT

+34 637217438

marcandorra92@gmail.com

Barcelona, 08021, Spain

Portfolio

Github

Linkedin

LANGUAGES

Catalan (native)

Spanish (native)

English (fluent)

French (basic)

Japanese (basic)

SKILLS

Machine Learning

Data Preprocessing, Regression, Classification, Bagging, Boosting, Deep Learning, Reinforcement Learning, Data Visualization.

Programming

Languages

Python, R, Java, C#, Javascript, PostgreSQL, MySQL.

Libraries

Pytorch, Tensorflow, SciPy, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-learn, Ggplot2.

MARC DABAD PLANAS

Multimedia Engineer

Result-driven Multimedia Engineer with professional experience in the gaming industry, banking industry, and teaching field. Currently focused on Data Science and Machine Learning projects involving state of the art research, data processing, model creation, data visualization and cloud services management.

EDUCATION

2021-2022 Master's Degree, Data Science

La Salle – Universitat Ramon Llull, Barcelona

2014-2015 Master's Degree, Multimedia Creation

La Salle – Universitat Ramon Llull, Barcelona

2010-2014 Bachelor's Degree, Multimedia Engineering

La Salle – Universitat Ramon Llull, Barcelona

WORK EXPERIENCE

2017-2021 King (Activision Blizzard). Barcelona

Mobile Game Company

Game Designer (R&D Department)

- Designed, analyzed, and documented +30 A/B tests to test hypothesis and to gather insights.
- Worked closely with data scientists and producers to monitor the KPIs and metrics of the product.
- Mentored 3 junior Game Designers by onboarding them and helping them to grow.

2015-2017 Freelance. Barcelona

Mobile Game Production

Game Developer

- Implemented 3 mobile games with Unity and launched them at Google Play and AppStore.

2014-2015 La Salle – Universitat Ramon Llull. Barcelona

Tech University

Unity Teacher

- Taught how to create videogames with Unity, in a class of +30 Multimedia Engineer students.

HCI Researcher

- Created 2 R&D projects that explored the interaction between people and objects.

2013-2014 GyD Iberica (Giesecke & Devrient). Barcelona

Credit Card Manufacturer

Junior Full-Stack Developer

- Worked in the IT department developing the intranet with ASP, MySQL, Javascript, HTML and CSS.
- All the content developed needed to handle, process, and update data from the Databases.